<addon id="plugin.video.hbogoeu" name="HBO GO EU" provider-name="arvvoid" version="2.0.10~beta26">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4" />
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3"/>
    <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="2.3.15" />
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="main.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="hr_HR">HBO GO EU</summary>
      <description lang="hr_HR">
Jednostavan, izvrstan Kodi dodatak za pristup HBO® Go EU sadržaju. (Ovaj dodatak nije službeno naručen / podržan od strane HBO-a.)

Važno, HBO® Go mora biti plaćen !!! Trebate valjani račun!
Registrirajte se na službenoj web stranici HBO® Go http://hbogo.eu

Trenutno podržava: Bosna i Hercegovina, Bugarska, Hrvatska, Češka, Mađarska, Makedonija, Crna Gora, Poljska, Portugal, Rumunjska, Srbija, Slovačka, Slovenija, Španjolska, Norveška, Danska, Švedska, Finska

Da biste prijavili greške ili zatražili pomoć s dodatkom, idite na: https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu
      </description>
      <disclaimer lang="hr_HR">
Ovaj dodatak nije službeno naručen / podržan od strane HBO-a. Zaštitni znak HBO® Go registriran je od strane Home Box Office, Inc. Za više informacija o HBO® Go Europe posjetite službenu web stranicu: http://hbogo.eu
NEMA JAMSTVA ZA DODATAK, MOŽE PRESTATI RADITI U BILO KOJEM TRENUTKU.
Ako je službena aplikacija dostupna za vašu platformu, preporučuje se da je koristite umjesto ovog add-on-a.
Svi sadržaji HBO Go-a © 2019 Copyright © 2017 Home Box Office, Inc. Sva prava pridržana.
      </disclaimer>
    <summary lang="en_GB">HBO GO EU</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">
Simple, great Kodi add-on to access HBO® Go EU content. (This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®.)

Important, HBO® Go must be paid for!!!  You need a valid account!
Register on the official HBO® Go website http://hbogo.eu

Curently support: Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Czech Republic, Hungary, Macedonia, Montenegro, Polonia, Portugal, Romania, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenija, Spain, Norway, Denmark, Sweden, Finland

To report bugs or request assistence with the add-on go to: https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu
    </description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®. The trademark HBO® Go is registered by Home Box Office, Inc. For more information on HBO® Go Europe visit the official website: http://hbogo.eu
THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE ADD-ON, IT CAN BREAK AND STOP WORKING AT ANY TIME.
If an official app is available for your platform, it's recommended to use it instead of this.
All HBO Go content is © 2019 Copyright © 2017 Home Box Office, Inc. All rights reserved.
    </disclaimer>
      <summary lang="hu_HU">HBO GO EU</summary>
      <description lang="hu_HU">

Egyszerű, nagy Kodi kiegészítő a HBO® Go EU tartalmának eléréséhez. (Ez a kiegészítő nem hivatalosan megbízott / támogatott a HBO® által.)

Fontos, hogy a HBO® Go-t meg kell fizetni !!! Érvényes fiókra van szüksége!
Regisztráljon a HBO® Go hivatalos honlapján http://hbogo.eu

Curently support: Bosznia és Hercegovina, Bulgária, Horvátország, Csehország, Magyarország, Macedónia, Montenegró, Polónia, Portugália, Románia, Szerbia, Szlovákia, Szlovénia, Spanyolország, Norvégia, Dánia, Svédország, Finnország

Ha hibákat vagy segítséget szeretne kérni a kiegészítő segítségével, látogasson el a következő oldalra: https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu
      </description>
      <disclaimer lang="hu_HU">
A HBO® nem támogatja ezt a kiegészítőt. A HBO® Go védjegyet a Home Box Office, Inc. regisztrálja. További információ a HBO® Go Europe webhelyről: http://hbogo.eu
A GARANCIA NEM TÁMOGATOTT, A KÖVETKEZŐ TÁMOGATÁS ÉS A MŰKÖDÉS ELLENŐRZÉSE.
Ha hivatalos alkalmazás áll rendelkezésre az Ön platformjára, javasoljuk, hogy használja ezt a helyett.
Minden HBO Go tartalom © 2019 Copyright © 2017 Home Box Office, Inc. Minden jog fenntartva.
      </disclaimer>
    <language>en hr hu pl</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=339798</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu</source>
    <website>https://arvvoid.github.io/plugin.video.hbogoeu</website>
    <news>
v.2.0.10-beta26
- Removed silent register api (removed on hbo go side)
- Initial individualization and device id get generated client side.

v.2.0.9-beta25
- Added Czech translation by Ike201

v.2.0.9-beta24
- Added Romanian translation by tmihai20
      
v.2.0.9-beta23
- HBO Spain+Nordic basic support (Spain, Norway, Denmark, Sweden, Finland)
      
v.2.0.8-beta22
- Enhanced media info

v.2.0.7-beta21
- Fix device ID if characters outside of ASCII are present

v.2.0.7-beta20
- Kids category and weekly top (might not be present for all countries)

v.2.0.7-beta19
- Credentials are no longer stored in cleartext and are encrypted using a calculated key from hardware info (this is not to be considered secure if your device is compromised the credentials should be considered compromised)
- Refresh session timer on reloading session

v.2.0.6-beta18
- Polish language added (contribution of kowalmisiek).
- Language files ID range fix

v.2.0.6-beta17
- Add to My List
- Remove from My List
- Rate Movies and TV Shows
- If OAuth unexpectedly fail for Operators with login redirection the add-on won't crash but display an informative message and write data that can help fix it to the debug log.

v.2.0.5-beta16
- Fixed a bug that prevented some countries from completing setup.
- Bumped inputstream.adaptive requirement to 2.3.15

v.2.0.5-beta15
- Minor fix.

v.2.0.5-beta14
- More robust categories listings. Solves #11 Portugal.

v.2.0.5-beta13
- Improved categories listings. Compatible with #11 Portugal.

v.2.0.4-beta12
- fix for #5 operators with login redirect (experimental need testing, please report)
- fix for #11 Portugal (experimental need testing, please report)
- bug fixes

v.2.0.3-beta11
- Fixed individualization/device storing. This bug caused needles device re-registration. (You can delete old registred devices, but don't have to do so, from your Hbo Go account, leave just the last registred one, the devices this add-on register will appear as Chrome 71 on Linux in Hbo Go)

v.2.0.3-beta10
- Country codes fix, flag api fix

v.2.0.3-beta9
- Guided user-friendly initial setup
- Code cleanup

v.2.0.2-beta8
- Added support for Portugal (web registration operators, and Vodafon TV operator)

v.2.0.1-beta7
- Minor cosmetic fixes

v.2.0.1-beta6
- Complete rewrite and restructure of the add-on (missed errors might be present, testing welcome)
- More robust login
- Persistent session
- Navigation improvemnts
- Correct views/media types (watched status shown)
- Structured to support multiple regions in the future, for now only http://hbogo.eu (covers 12 countries) is implemented

v.2.0-beta5
- Code cleaning
- Additional settings
- WORK IN PROGRESS: Translations

v.2.0-beta4
- Persistent session

v.2.0-beta3
- Code cleaning
- More info in debug log
- Option to force original movie/episode names
- EXPERT OPTION: Show episode/movie names in scraper friendly format (useful only for some external library integration addons)

v.2.0-beta2
- More info in debug log
- Providers using redirection login are identified (preparation for implementation of that login method)

v.2.0-beta1
- Added support for all hbogo.eu: Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Czech Republic, Hungary, Macedonia, Montenegro, Polonia, Romania, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenija
- Minor bugfixes

v.1.3.1.EU
- Minor bugfixes

v.1.3.EU
- Language of retrived HBO Go Eu content is set from currently loaded language file

v.1.2.EU
- Added support for Hungary

v.1.1.EU
- First General HBO Go Eu Realease
- Added support for Croatia
    </news>
    <assets>
     <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
     <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
     <screenshot>resources/screen1.png</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen7.png</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen8.png</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
